export let question = [
  {
    question: "What is the name of Meta's Founder?",
    choice1: "Mark Zuckerbeg",
    choice2: "Mark Zuckerberg",
    choice3: "Mark Zuckerbreg",
    choice4: "Mark Zuckerbarg",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Mcrosoft's Founder?",
    choice1: "Bill Gate",
    choice2: "Elon Musk",
    choice3: "Karim Benzema",
    choice4: "Mark Zukerbarg",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "In which HTML tag do we write javascript code?",
    choice1: "js",
    choice2: "mscript",
    choice3: "script",
    choice4: "i",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "In which HTML tag do we write css code?",
    choice1: "js",
    choice2: "style",
    choice3: "script",
    choice4: "i",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is odd ?",
    choice1: "Python",
    choice2: "PHP",
    choice3: "MYSQL",
    choice4: "JAVA",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is a scripting language ?",
    choice1: "C++",
    choice2: "C#",
    choice3: "PHP",
    choice4: "JAVA",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What's the name of the machine which helps compile java code ?",
    choice1: "JVM",
    choice2: "JMV",
    choice3: "MJV",
    choice4: "APK",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "When writing a java code the class name must be equivalent with the file name ?",
    choice1: "Yes",
    choice2: "No",
    choice3: "Maybe",
    choice4: "I don't think so",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "PHP is a recursive achronym for ?",
    choice1: "Personal Home Page",
    choice2: "Proper HTML Preprocessor",
    choice3: "Hypertext Preprocesor",
    choice4: "Point Header Parser",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "The Father of Java is ?",
    choice1: "Guido Van Rossum",
    choice2: "James Gosling",
    choice3: "Linus Torvaldo",
    choice4: "Harry Kane",
    answer: 2,
  },
];
